# **Cody Stair**

♥ Clinton, TN 

staircody27@gmail.com 

https://codystair.github.io 

codystair

## **Summary**

I'm a Software Engineer based in Knoxville, TN. I'm the co-creator of Stagehand ②, a drop-in framework that automates the deployment and management of review apps for modern frontend applications. I have multiple years of experience in both the JavaScript and Ruby ecosystems, as well as Amazon Web Services (AWS) and Google Cloud Platform (GCP).

#### **Skills**

Backend	Frontend	Tooling	Cloud
Ruby, Rails, Sinatra,	HTML/CSS, JavaScript,	Git/GitHub, GitHub	AWS, Digital Ocean,
Node.js, PostgreSQL,	jQuery, React, Next,	Actions, Linux, Jira,	Heroku, Google Cloud
Express, RESTful APIs	GraphQL, TypeScript	Codefresh	Platform

### **Professional Experience**

2021 – present Ful	ll Stack Engineer, MotoRefi
--------------------	-----------------------------

- Developed and maintained our company's internal applications
- Migrated our entire marketing site from using GraphCMS to Contentful
- Developed design documents and proof of concepts for various engineering initiatives
- Designed and implemented a large data migration from a Google Firestore collection to a PostgreSQL database
- Explored and implemented a solution to a header injection security vulnerbility in our system
- Helped decouple the frontend of a large Rails app and rebuilt it in React/Next
- Collaborated daily with the engineering team, product team, and other departments

#### 2020 – 2021 **Co-Creator, Software Engineer,** Stagehand ☑

- Co-created Stagehand, an open-source drop-in solution that automates review apps for frontend applications
- Designed cloud infrastructure on AWS to host frontend review apps
- Prototyped and built GitHub integration to automatically deploy and tear down review apps using GitHub Actions
- Automated provisioning of AWS infrastructure using AWS CloudFormation
- Implemented client-side functionality for review apps to provide dashboard and handle routing using HTML iframe elements and service workers
- Built a robust easy-to-use CLI that abstracts away configuration and deployment logic, available as an NPM package
- Collaborated daily with a 100% remote team of engineers
- Co-authored Stagehand's case study: https://stagehand-framework.github.io ☑

#### **Software Engineer,** Self-Employed

• Developed mostly open-source software using Rails, Sinatra, Ruby, Node.js, Express, PostgreSQL, React/Redux, vanilla JavaScript, HTML, and CSS

## **Education**

2017 - 2020

2011 – 2013 Liberty University

Bachelor of Arts - BA, Religion/Religious Studies